A welcome to my channel Winners Portfolio
of I am your friend Ramesh Babu, my
channel I request only quality companies,
this staff will
create a huge bank for you in the long term, if
you come to my channel for the first time then
subscribe to my channel and
also watch my old video once, you will get a lot of benefit, today
in this video I will tell you about a great company, I will
tell you about a number one group company,
invest as much money as you want in this company, it is a
very good company for doing SIP for
retirement,
forget investing money in this company for children's marriage, it is a debt
free company, in this company you will
get the benefit of the company in the long term, it
is an acceptable company, in the coming 10-15 years
you will create a huge will,
this is my portfolio stocks, I am
not only on YouTube, I am an investor,
first of all,
after doing this, I
request that company, the name of this company is
serial number General Insurance Company,
50 ghee in the city rs.32 today current market price
₹50, till date I have been looted by 10% profit in this company  The
company will not survive for 10-15 years. The balance sheet of this company is
very good. If you
invest in a company with a similar balance sheet, then there is no need to be afraid. Do
not invest money in the company even by mistake. Now if the
money gets wasted, it is an
acceptable company. Invest in this company and
forget it. Now it will become such
that even if the market falls, the company will
not fall much. Keep investing in it in every fall. There is
no need to be afraid. In the coming 10-15
years, you will have created a huge will.
Look at the business of the company, it is so long and
general insurance has over four crore customers.
Then in today's development, this company will do car
insurance, travel insurance,
life insurance, if insurance will do
two wheeler insurance,
elected president insurance, business
insurance, railway insurance.
This is the number one company in the insurance system. It is a
very big and excellent company in general insurance. This is a
company that benefits you. If you
invest in such a company, then there is no need to be afraid.
In our India, there are very few people who do life insurance,
health insurance,
and people who invest in mutual funds are
also very few. People who invest in the stock market are
also very few in the coming times.
In 10-15 years, 14 sectors like life incidents,
general insurance, mutual fund business,
broking business will
get huge benefits.
Which company's city I have 120%
equity in this company till date. One
leg of my money is that the fall in 2016 is Russia.
In the coming 10-15 years, there are chances of me creating a huge fortune in this company. I like this
company. It is
possible that I will not sit idle for the coming 10-15 years
or if it falls, I will
buy more. This company has
very high chances of growing at 35 percent CAGR every year for the coming 10-15 years. It will
give 35 percent return every year for the coming 10-15 years. The duration is 15 years.
A big magic of compounding.
After 15 years, my money will become faluda and become 6
to lax. There is
a Buddhist save company. Similarly, if
you invest money in a company having balance sheet, then there is
no need to be afraid
in the coming 10-15 years.  But forget about it for 15 years, I will
create a huge Will
in a sexy video and I will
meet you with Shahrukh Khan, till then bye-bye,
thank you.